quantumworkplace.com 2017-07-01

# Privacy Policy | Quantum Workplace

Quantum Workplace is committed to the highest standard of privacy. This includes the privacy of individuals and organizations that take our surveys (survey respondents), individuals who use our Employee Feedback Platform (users), and individuals who visit Quantum Workplace’s websites (visitors). This privacy policy explains how Quantum Workplace handles personal and company data for those using our services and tools.

### Survey Respondents

Quantum Workplace protects the privacy of individuals taking our employee surveys, Best Places to Work surveys, and research surveys. We will not share, sell, rent, swap, or authorize any third party to use survey respondents' email addresses for commercial purposes. Our surveys are strictly confidential. Our business depends upon confidential survey feedback, and we do everything we can to protect the individuals and organizations that take our surveys.

###### Employee Surveys

We will not in any way reprint, resell, or redistribute your organization’s survey results to anyone, with the exception of Best Places to Work surveys, in which case results are shared with the event’s sponsoring publication.

Access to your organization’s results is available to selected leaders within your organization who use the information for organizational development purposes. Organizational data may be sliced by employee demographics, but will never identify individual employees or employee groups with fewer than five employees.

When our surveys ask for demographic information, it is for benchmarking purposes and to allow employers to view aggregate results by age, department, gender, etc. However, if a demographic has fewer than five people, employers will not be able to see the results. For example, if an employer wanted to see the results of ONLY the marketing department, but the marketing department has fewer than five employees, employers wouldn’t be 

able

view the results of this demographic. This is how we keep survey responses confidential.

For population and pulse surveys, employers will NOT have access to:

  * Employee names or email addresses – a survey cannot be tracked to a specific person
  * The ability to see who has or has not completed the survey
  * A specific employee’s answers

For self-evaluation surveys, such as an exit interview or new hire surveys, employers WILL have access to:

  * The ability to see if the self evaluator (exiter or new hire) has completed the survey
  * A specific self evaluator’s (exiting or new employee’s) answers

Quantum Workplace reserves the right to aggregate your data into comparative benchmarks that are presented to our clients or third parties. Under all circumstances, your organization’s data will be combined with multiple organizations, and your organization’s identity will never be revealed.

###### Best Places to Work

In addition to the policies listed above in Employee Surveys, Quantum Workplace also maintains the following policies when operating Best Places to Work surveys.

Quantum Workplace reserves the right to share Best Places to Work organizations’ information with the sponsoring publication to establish honorees and awards. If your organization is not an honoree, your results will not be shared.

All participating Best Places to Work organizations will receive a one-page overview report after participating in the contest. This report will show the overall score and a few specific highlights from the survey. Employers also have the option to purchase a more advanced report that will contain all survey results and comments. However, answers are always shown at the aggregate level (grouped together).

###### Research Surveys

We will not in any way reprint, resell, or redistribute an individual’s survey response or an organization’s results to anyone. Data we collect for research is always published and distributed in aggregate.

Quantum Workplace reserves the right to aggregate your data into comparative benchmarks that are presented to our clients or third parties. Under all circumstances, your data and your organization’s data will be combined with multiple organizations, and neither identity will be revealed.

When our surveys ask for demographic information, it is for benchmarking purposes and to allow our research studies to examine aggregate results by age, department, gender, etc.

### Users

Quantum Workplace protects the privacy of individuals who use our Employee Feedback Platform. We will not sell, license, trade, or rent your personal information.

###### Account Information

When user accounts are set up, we collect and store information about you, including your name, email address, and password. We use this information to set up your account and allow communication with you regarding your account.

###### Product Usage

When you’re logged into our Employee Feedback Platform, we collect and store information that you submit through the website for your use and for your disclosure to other users in your organization as part of your use of the product. This would 

include,

but is not limited to, information, such as a commitment in Engagement, a recognition post in Recognition, a goal update in Goals, or a comment in a Feedback cycle. Which information is private and which information is public to other users inside our tools is determined by the settings you or your organization have selected.

###### Technical Data

Quantum Workplace may collect and use technical data and related information, including but not limited to, technical information about your device, system, application software, and peripherals, to facilitate the provision of software updates, product support, and to allow us to continually make improvements to our products and services. This information is never tied to an individual user.

### Visitors

Quantum Workplace protects the privacy of individuals who visit our websites. This policy applies to websites that link to this privacy policy, including all quantumworkplace.com sites and subdomains.

When you create an account or submit other information on our websites, we collect and store that information, such as your name, title, email address, and password. We use this information to set up your account and to allow administration and communication with you regarding your account. We may also use your email address to send you updates and provide services to you. We will not share, sell, rent, swap, or authorize any third party to use users’ email addresses for commercial purposes.

###### Google AdWords

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an inquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Quantum Workplace website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

### EU-US Privacy Shield

Quantum Workplace’s processes adhere to the EU-US Privacy Shieldprinciples of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. To view our certification and to learn more about the Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield program, visit [Privacy Shield](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome). As a part of this program, we are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission and we are liable for the onward transfer of personal information to third parties. Furthermore, we are required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities and must meet national security requirements. We do not disclose personal information to third parties. Should that change in the future, we will provide individuals the option to opt-out of having their information disclosed to third parties for purposes that are materially different for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized. The company administrator has a right to access personal information and has the ability to correct, amend, or delete that information where it is inaccurate or has been processed in violation of the Privacy Shield principles.

In compliance with Privacy Shield, Quantum Workplace is committed to resolving complaints in a timely manner. Individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact Quantum Workplace at [hello@quantumworkplace.com](mailto:hello@quantumworkplace.com). If we are unable to satisfactorily resolve any privacy or data concerns, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider [JAMS](https://www.jamsadr.com/). Under certain conditions, you may have the right to invoke binding arbitration.
